http://www.infrared.com/privacy-policy

Sign InCreate AccountOrdersMy AccountSigned in as:filler@godaddy.comOrdersMy AccountSign outHomeInfoAbout UsWhat Is Infrared?WarrantyTerms of UsePrivacy PolicyOur SoftwareSolutionsAnti-TerrorismSecurity & SurveillanceMarine & CoastalMilitary/Law EnforcementWildland Fire DetectionRailroad Fire DetectionProductsSpecialsSystemsServicesInspection SurveyHotspot DetectionContactMoreHomeInfoAbout UsWhat Is Infrared?WarrantyTerms of UsePrivacy PolicyOur SoftwareSolutionsAnti-TerrorismSecurity & SurveillanceMarine & CoastalMilitary/Law EnforcementWildland Fire DetectionRailroad Fire DetectionProductsSpecialsSystemsServicesInspection SurveyHotspot DetectionContactSign InCreate AccountOrdersMy AccountSigned in as:filler@godaddy.comOrdersMy AccountSign outSigned in as:filler@godaddy.comHomeInfoSolutionsProductsServicesContactAccountOrdersMy AccountSign outSign InOrdersMy Account
Privacy Policy US INFRARED INCORPORATED SITE PRIVACY POLICYThis Privacy Policy Statement outlines the obligations of US Infrared Incorporated regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of information collected from you by means of US Infrared Incorporated’s network of Web properties (collectively the “US Infrared Incorporated Site”). By using the US Infrared Incorporated Site you consent to the collection and use of your information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy Statement. If you do not want your information to be collected and used in the manner described in this Privacy Policy Statement, you can opt out by not participating in the US Infrared Incorporated Site.Information that US Infrared Incorporated CollectsUS Infrared Incorporated may collect information from all users of the US Infrared Incorporated Site, except as described below. What information we collect and how we use it, depends upon your activity on the US Infrared Incorporated Site.Children’s Privacy PolicyUS Infrared Incorporated does not knowingly collect the personally identifiable information of children under the age of thirteen. Because US Infrared Incorporated is committed to protecting children’s privacy online, use of the US Infrared Incorporated Site by children under the age of thirteen who live in the United States is prohibited.VisitingUS Infrared Incorporated may collect non-personally identifiable, anonymous information from all visitors to the US Infrared Incorporated Site. Examples of the types of anonymous information that US Infrared Incorporated may collect includes a user’s IP address, browser type, and the date and time a user accessed the US Infrared Incorporated Site. We may use this anonymous information for system administration purposes in order to enhance the operation of the US Infrared Incorporated Site and make it more useful to visitors. We may share this information with outside parties, but each user’s personal identity remains anonymous.From time to time, we may use an outside agent to collect anonymous user information. The collection and use of such information will be for purposes substantially identical to those described above. As part of this service, the outside agent may use cookies.RegistrationTo use certain features of the US Infrared Incorporated Site, you may be required to first complete a registration procedure which requires you to provide certain personal information, such as your name and email address (providing demographic information, such as your job title, is optional). US Infrared Incorporated collects this information and uses it internally for purposes such as marketing, customer administration, technical administration of the US Infrared Incorporated Site, or to contact you. US Infrared Incorporated does not share this information with outside parties except as indicated in the ‘Information Sharing’ section below.Other InformationUS Infrared Incorporated may, from time to time, collect other information from you (for instance, when we make special offers, hold promotions, or conduct surveys). Information collected by these means is used internally for purposes such as marketing, customer administration, technical administration of the US Infrared Incorporated Site, or to contact you. US Infrared Incorporated does not share this information with outside parties except as indicated in the ‘Information Sharing’ section below.CookiesUS Infrared Incorporated uses cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data placed on your computer's hard drive by US Infrared Incorporated that can transmit your information to us. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie terminates automatically after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive, but can be removed by following the directions on your browser. You can set your browser to disable cookies, but this may prevent you from enjoying all of the features of the US Infrared Incorporated Site. We use cookies to deliver content that is specific to your interests, to streamline the login process, and to collect anonymous user data in the aggregate. The cookies make your use of the US Infrared Incorporated Site easier, allow you to retrieve an earlier shopping cart, make the US Infrared Incorporated Site run more smoothly, and help us to maintain the security of the US Infrared Incorporated Site. Some outside parties may use cookies on the US Infrared Incorporated Site (for example, banner advertisers). US Infrared Incorporated has no access to or control over these cookies.Information SharingExcept as set forth in this Privacy Policy Statement, US Infrared Incorporated does not disclose your personally identifiable information to outside parties. US Infrared Incorporated may partner with other outside parties to provide specific services. When a user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. US Infrared Incorporated uses great care in selecting business partners with whom we share your information. However, US Infrared Incorporated is not a guarantor of outside parties’ practices regarding your information.  Users of the US Infrared Incorporated Site permit the sharing of their personal information at their own risk, and shall not hold US Infrared Incorporated responsible for acts or omissions of outside parties. US Infrared Incorporated will disclose your information when we believe in good faith that it is legally required, such as pursuant to a warrant, subpoena, or court order, or to protect our rights and property. In the event that US Infrared Incorporated is acquired by or merged into another company, all information collected will be transferred to the acquiring company as one of US Infrared Incorporated's assets and will be governed by the acquiring company's privacy policy, if any.SecurityUS Infrared Incorporated takes precautions to protect our users’ information both online and offline. We also protect user information offline. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a user service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information.Correction/Updating Personal Information, Opting-out, and Contacting US Infrared Incorporated You may use the contact information provided below to request a change in your personal information (such as an address correction) or to have your personal information removed from our database. We will correct, update, or remove your personal data according to your request. You may also use the contact information below if you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy Statement or your dealings with the US Infrared Incorporated Site.US Infrared, Inc.
59 Damonte Ranch Pkwy Suite B-265
Reno, NV 89521 USA
info@infrared.comNotification of ChangesUS Infrared Incorporated may change this Privacy Policy Statement from time to time for any reason. When we make such changes, we will post notification of them on our main page. Your continued use of this site after notification of such changes have been posted shall constitute your assent to be bound by these changes.ASSENT BY USING THE US INFRARED INCORPORATED WEBSITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ THIS AGREEMENT AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY ITS TERMS.
Copyright © 2020 US Infrared Inc. - All Rights Reserved.Terms of UsePrivacy Policy
